Merged Etl: C:\dev\PC\_evidence\deeptest\g80sh-deep-0924-deep1.etl
The trace you have just captured "C:\dev\PC\_evidence\deeptest\g80sh-deep-0924-deep1.etl" may contain personally identifiable information, including but not necessarily limited to paths to files accessed, paths to registry accessed and process names. Exact information depends on the events that were logged. Please be aware of this when sharing out this trace with other people.
